The first important thing is the establishment of this mesoderm.
首先重要的一点是中胚层的形成。
We have the primitive streak appearing, we have the notochordal axis,
原始线出现，我们有脊索轴，
and we see that there is an aspiration field between the ectodermal tissue and the
我们看到外胚层组织和内胚层组织之间存在一个吸引场，
endodermal tissue,
内胚层组织，
and that there is a movement where a space will be filled.
并且存在一个运动，其中将有一个空间被填充。
So that means that the mesodermal tissue originates from the
所以这意味着中胚层组织起源于
ectodermal tissue,
外胚层组织，
but which is not yet...
但它还不是...
an ectodermal tissue, which is an epiblastic tissue.
外胚层组织，它是一种上胚层组织。
The bottle cells are attracted towards the center,
瓶状细胞被吸引到中心，
and that's how this space between the epiblastic and hypoblastic tissue
正是这样，上胚层组织和下胚层组织之间的这个空间
will become the primitive mesenchymal tissue, the future mesoderm.
将成为原始间充质组织，即未来的中胚层。
It is again the notochord that will influence this process.
又是脊索影响了这个过程。
It's an electric field, again.
这又是一个电场。
Last time, we worked at the sacrum level,
上次我们研究了骶骨，
and I asked you to place yourselves on the axis.
我让你们专注于脊索轴。
notochordal. Now we're going to go a little further, we're going to try to go
脊索轴。现在我们要更进一步，我们将尝试去
see, since my notochord is here, what we call Hensen's node, which
看，因为我的脊索在这里，我们称之为恩森结，它
comes to make
会形成
a wave movement, which is a cranio-caudal movement, we could say,
一个波浪运动，这是一个颅尾方向的运动，
there is like a
就像一个
gradual regression of my primitive streak backwards. This primitive streak
我的原始线逐渐向后退化。这条原始线
will
将
be found at the level of the sacro-coccygeal base, if you will, the
位于骶尾骨基部，如果你愿意，就是
vestige.
遗迹。
energetic. We see that I have all my mesoderm in place.
能量的。我们看到我的中胚层已经完全形成。
We're going to do a practice.
我们将进行一次练习。
We're going to go towards this coccyx because we could say that this will be found
我们将走向尾骨，因为我们可以说这将被
concentrated on this
集中在这个
small area. The first impulse will be on the hypoblastic tissue.
小区域。第一次冲动将作用于下胚层组织。
And it is only there
只有在那里
that the epiblast will become...
上胚层才会变成...
The hypoderm, the hypoblast, will become endoderm.
下胚层，下胚层，将变成内胚层。
So that means that it is my epiblast that informs all of my
所以这意味着是我的上胚层告知了我所有的
tissues,
组织，
which itself is completely integrated by my notochord.
它本身完全被我的脊索整合。
So it's an electromagnetic field that will inform your body.
所以这是一个电磁场，它将告知你的身体。
You understand why I say we put people back on earth,
你明白我为什么说我们让人们脚踏实地，
we put people back in their bodies.
我们让人们回到身体里。
When we touch with consciousness,
当我们有意识地触摸时，
At this level, we are in this force that the body has established.
在这个层面上，我们处于身体所建立的这种力量之中。
I find myself here with, this time, the second impulse, the second wave that
我在这里，这次是第二次冲动，第二次波浪，
is given here,
在这里给出，
which will form my mesodermal tissue.
它将形成我的中胚层组织。
So I find myself with information, initially notochordal,
所以我最初得到的是脊索信息，
which will give the information with my primitive streak,
它将通过我的原条给出信息，
this aspiration field that creates this space of my
这个吸力场创造了我的原条空间，
primitive streak,
原条，
in relation to...
相对于...
in fact, in contact with the establishment of my embryonic pedicle
实际上是与我的胚胎蒂的形成以及我的渗透和灌注场的组织化接触。
and my fields of permeation and infusion and permeation that are organizing.
所以正是在这个运动中，我的中胚层得到了整合。
So it is in this movement that I have an integration of my mesoderm.
那么，我们现在处于第14天到第16天之间。
So there, we are between the 14th day and the 16th day.
当你开始时，你会发现你首先有
When you place yourself, you will realize that you first have
这种太极般的，这种脊索波，
this kind of tai chi, this notochordal wave,
然后下面，
and then below,
与此同时，我在另一边也有这个，它在下面形成了一种侵入，你明白吗？
At the same time as I have this, on the other side, it creates an
所以如果可以的话，我有一种双重运动。
invasion underneath, you see.
所以它就像这样。
So I have a kind of double movement, if you will.
你把手放在骶骨上或者放在尾骨上。
So it goes like this.
之后，我们将在心脏层面选取其他非常特定的平衡点，我们将会看到。
You place yourself on the sacrum or on the coccyx.
心脏的推定方面是由这个场决定的。